Guide to the Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania Records, 1945-1984 AIS.1984.28
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania Records
1945-1984
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania
AIS.1984.28
20 Linear Feet (16 boxes)
The Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania represented employees of telephone companies throughout Pennsylvania. This collection contains correspondence and reports regarding the activities of the Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania.
Previous Citation
Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania Records, 1945-1984, AIS.1984.28, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Communication Workers of America, Local 13000 in 1984.
History
The Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania (FTWP) represented employees of telephone companies throughout Pennsylvania. In 1984, the FTWP merged with the Communication Workers of America to form CWA Local 13000. Frank Wentzel was president of the Pittsburgh Division of the FTWP and was responsible for leading the union into the CWA, where he served as an assistant to two CWA vice presidents.
Scope and Content Notes
This collection contains correspondence and reports regarding the activities of the Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania. Included is information on affiliation debates, committee meetings, and telephone technologies. The files document local, district and statewide issues and events, such as working conditions, elections and company reorganization.
Labor unions -- Pennsylvania; Labor; Records (Documents); Minutes (Administrative records); Contracts; Correspondence; Constitutions; Financial records; Telephone companies -- Employees -- Labor unions -- Pennsylvania; Communications Workers of America. Local 13000 (Philadelphia, Pa.); Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania; Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania
- Health Plans, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Contract Labor, Second Quarter, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Construction of Minutes (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Meter Reading by Phone (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Mechanized Time (Box 1, Folder 5)
- MATCH Program (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Sales Program (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Surplus Food Distribution Program, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Strike, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Coffee Stops, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Centrex (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Centralized Records (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Call-Thru Procedure (Box 1, Folder 13)
- C.A.B. (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Unemployment Compensation, 1962-1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Bulletin Boards, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Slow Down, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- S.C. Relays in Trunk Hunting, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Metro (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Local Presidents' Conference, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Management by Objectives (MBO) (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Hiring (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Civil Rights, Bell Agreement, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Picturephone, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Productivity Clause Proposed, Illinois Bell (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Phone Store (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Phone Centers (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Phase II, PBX Control (Box 2, Folder 3)
- PBX Inventory Group (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Pitt Students (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Quality of Work Life: What's in a Name? by Ted Mills, 1978 (Box 2, Volume 1)
- Government Report on American Telephone and Telegraph Company's Compliance with the Consent Decree, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Bell System Reorganization (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Correspondence on Legislation (Box 2, Folder 8)
- AT&T Organizational Structure (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Telecommunications International Union Financial Statements, December 31, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Telecommunications International Union Second Annual Convention, June 5-7, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Line Status Verifier (LSV) (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Report on Occupational Stress in the Bell System (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Legislation and Politics, 1964-1966, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 14-16)
- Organizing General Engineers (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Plant Closings: Resources for Public Officials and Activists, May 1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Frank Wentzel (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Palatized Cable (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Occasional and Temporary Employment (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Explanation of Pension Reform Act of 1974 by FTWP (Box 2, Volume 2)
- Tribute and Forms for Public Occasions by David Belson, 1951 (Box 2, Volume 3)
- Labor Scrap-Book by United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum & Plastic Workers of America (Box 2, Volume 4)
- Organizing (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Grievance Summary, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
- Telecommunications International Union, National Trends in Collective Bargaining, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Correspondence regarding Dues Deduction (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Dues Increase Information, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Dues Deductions and Restructuring, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Referendum, Communication Workers of America Affiliation, February 16, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Letters to the Executive Office (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Contract Referendums, 1950-1970 (Box 3, Folder 9-14)
- Strike Vote and Contract Referendum, 1980, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 15-16)
- Representatives Election, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Local Office and Division Officers, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Assessment Records, 1952, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 19-20)
- Budgets (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Union Business Payment Basis (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Reports for Bureau of Labor Standards (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Votes, 1952-1974 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Two Level Structure (Box 3, Folder 25)
- W.A.R.P. Expenses, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Proposed Branch Structure, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- William S. Leary Testimonial Dinner, August 15, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Flood Disaster Fund, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Voter Registration, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- City of Hope Information, 1962-1964 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Miscellaneous Information (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Original News Columns, Pittsburgh Division (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Sophie, Election Information (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Correspondence regarding Elections, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Program and Forms regarding Elections (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Services Department and Contract Letters (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Summer Help Information, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Notices and Letters to Representatives and Job Stewards (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Notices, Pittsburgh Division Membership (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Phone Stores, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- National Council of Senior Citizens, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Elections (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Miscellaneous Information, 1949-1950, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Elections, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Interim Elections, 1975-1979 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- State Safety Committee, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Drug Abuse Pamphlets, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- State Association of Boroughs (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Butler Settlement, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Bargaining, 1968, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
- Bridge Lifting Units (Box 4, Folder 5)
- General Services Organization Charts, 1967-1976 (Box 4, Folder 6-7)
- Assessment, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Corporate Staff, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Special Services Management Bureau (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Satellite (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Saturday Holiday (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Constitution Rewrite (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Election Procedures, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Reproduction Bureau (Box 4, Folder 15-16)
- Repair Service Operation (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Mini Computers (Box 4, Folder 18)
- United Way, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 19-20)
- Volunteer Firemen (Box 4, Folder 21)
- S.O.M.P. (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Schedules (Box 4, Folder 23-25)
- Service Analysts (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Union Positions (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Rita Kolesar Unemployment Compensation Case (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Joseph Herwatic (Box 4, Folder 29)
- MAC Questions (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Mico Brake (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Right to Work Materials, 1960-1969 (Box 4, Folder 32-34)
- Division Council Local 41 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Election Rules (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Election Committees (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Lawrence Gigliotti, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Division Minutes, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Elections, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Added Mainline, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Grievance Reports, Convention, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Force Work Load, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Vacations, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Automation, 1959-1966 (Box 4, Folder 45-47)
- Miscellaneous Information, 1975, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Strike, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 49-50)
- Food Stamps (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Forbes Health Maintenance Plan, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 52-54)
- FTWP News Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Fair Labor Standards Act (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Flood Relief, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Fair Labor Practices Act (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Firemen Amendment 9A (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Fringe Benefits (Box 4, Folder 60)
- 4E Digital Switcher, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Frameman A, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Buildings Work Jurisdiction, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Division Harmony (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
- Locals 40, 41, 42,43, and 44 Harmony (Box 5, Folder 5-9)
- Election Results, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 10-11)
- Local President (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous Information (Box 5, Folder 13)
- C.O.P.E., 1960-1964, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 14-15)
- Construction Force Distribution (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Constitutional Interpretations (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Confidential Clerks (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Community Service (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Committee for Higher Public Education (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Communications Labor Act (Box 5, Folder 21-22)
- City of Hope (Box 5, Folder 23-25)
- Citizens for PA Constitution (Box 5, Folder 26)
- C.T.I., 1976 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Company Reorganization Plan, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Company Redistricting Plan and How It Affects FTWP (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Greater Pittsburgh Labor-Management Advisory Council, 1961-1970, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 30-31)
- Proposal to Promote and Educate the HMO Concept, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Forbes Health System, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 33-34)
- Home Rule Charter, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Holidays, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Craft Conferences, 1963, 1973, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 37-42)
- Force Forecast, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Convention Materials (Box 5, Folder 44-48)
- Contract Merger Committee (Box 5, Folder 49-50)
- Forbes Health Management Plan, 1977-1980 (Box 5, Folder 51-57)
- Labor Advisory Committee and Grievance Procedure, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Civil Rights (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Clippings, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Dimension PBX (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Group Insurance Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania (Box 6, Folder 3)
- American Medical Association, 1961-1965 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- F.C.C. Investigation (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Force Distribution (Box 6, Folder 6)
- General Services (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Installer and Repairmen Flexibility (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Force Adjustment (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Grievances, 1962-1971, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 10-11)
- 1A Home Interphone (Box 6, Folder 12)
- HD Days, Part Time Employees, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Holidays (Box 6, Folder 14-15)
- I.C. Glendenning Testimony (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Human Relations Meetings (Box 6, Folder 17)
- 4A Tolls Sets (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Competition (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Insurance Union (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Two Level Union Structure (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Carter Phone (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Local, Division and Representative Elections, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 23-25)
- Representatives, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Election Program, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Additional Delegate, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Division President, Vice President and Local Offices Elections, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 29-30)
- Representatives Elections, 1976, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 31-32)
- Division and Local Officers Elections, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 33-37)
- Group Insurance (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Executive Board, 1961-1962, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- PACT Committee, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Executive Administration Meeting, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Arbitration, American Arbitration Association, 1978, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Labor Relations, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Division Council, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Elections, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Joint Meetings, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Part-Timing and Over-Timing, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Connecticut Union of Telephone Workers, 1973-1974, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- History of the American Labor Movement Booklets, 1964, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Miscellaneous Financial Records and Evaluations (Box 6, Folder 50)
- FTWP Manuals, 1967, 1970-1973, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Miscellaneous Pamphlets and Booklets, 1954, 1965, 1967-1982 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- "'Ma' Bell is a Cheap Mother" Stickers (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Agreement between Bell Telephone Company and Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1980 (Box 6, Volume 1-2)
- "Telephone Work for Telephone Workers" Medallion (Box 6, Item 1)
- Employment Outlook, Telephone Occupations (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Alliance of Independent Telephone Unions, 1957, 1972-1976 (Box 7, Folder 2-3)
- Futuristic Committee (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Communication Workers Proposals to Executive Board, January 13, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Alliance for Labor Action (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Accounting Affiliation Petition, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- United Auto Workers, January 12, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, January 11, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Communication Workers of America, January 13, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Organizing (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Affiliation, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania Restructure, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- United Farm Workers (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Telecommunications International Union, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Elections, 1949, 1951, 1954-1955, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Penn State Labor Library Committee (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Agency Shop (Box 7, Folder 18)
- CSMS Concept, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- BS-CS Group Assignments (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Selection of BS-CS Personnel (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Local 43 Pittsburgh Division Joint Meeting, B. Bruggerworth, June 24, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania Forms (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Proposed Branch Structure, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Branch Structure, 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Branch Changes, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Branch and Local Structure, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- New Non-Management Title, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Free Phone (Box 7, Folder 29)
- LMOS Pittsburgh Meeting (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Election Rules (Box 7, Folder 31)
- 800 A PBX, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Election Results, Representatives (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Division President and Local Officers Election, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Local Presidents Elections, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Representatives Elections, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Local President Elections (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Participation in Biennial Election, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Elevator Conversion (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Division President and Local Officer Elections, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Encyclopedia Britannica (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Equal Employment Law (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Economic Opportunity Act (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Agency: Dues, Non-Members, Resignation Dues, 1948-1949, 1953, 1957, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- AT&T, American Bell, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Associated Builders and Contractors and Full Force, 1963, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Calendars, 1976 (Box 7, Item 1)
- Agreement between Bell Telephone Company and Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1971 (Box 7, Item 2)
- Temporary and Occasional Work Reports (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
- Differentials (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Projected Job Vacancies, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Telecommunications International Union Health Care (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Government Report on American Telephone and Telegraph Company's Compliance with the Consent Decree (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Telecommunications International Union Report on Communications Union Canada (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Report on Occupational Stress in the Bell System (Box 8, Folder 8)
- One Man Line Crew (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Truck Weights (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Occupation Tax (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Temporary Transfer Expenses (Box 8, Folder 12)
- State Organization Chart (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Technological Trends (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Time Off for Funeral (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Bell TWX Acquisition, 1964, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- The New Wage and Hour Law, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Work Rules (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Work Stoppages (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Wage and Hour Interpretation (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Wage Freeze and Progression (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Grievance Forms (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Grape Boycott (Box 8, Folder 23)
- General Services (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Grievance Summary, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Wages (Box 8, Folder 26)
- New Traffic Report (Box 8, Folder 27)
- McFarland, 7th Avenue (Box 8, Folder 28)
- R. Balash, 7th Avenue (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Motor Vehicle Check List (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Management Promotions Method (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Go-No Go (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Grievance Mechanics (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Pending Grievances (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Gun Control (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Local 45 Grievances (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Local 42 Grievances (Box 8, Folder 37-38)
- Local 41 Grievances (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Miscellaneous Local and Division Records (Box 9, Folder 1)
- TELSAM Service Analyst (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Tours (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Tuition Aid (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Traffic Service Position (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Thru Testing (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Titles (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Temporary Test Center Employees (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Traffic Organizing (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Traffic Tabulating Department (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Prelich Grievance, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Membership Records (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Medical Visit Expenses (Box 9, Folder 13)
- McGuire Scholarship, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Forced United Way Contributions Article, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Work Stoppage, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Titles, Job Content (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous Reports and Notes (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Time Off for Union Business (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Test Center (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Tapes (Box 9, Folder 21)
- American Arbitration Association Case, December 17, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 22-23)
- Quality of Work Life Steering Committee (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Communication Workers of America Q&A, Committee on the Future (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Health Protection for Operators of VDTs/CRTs (Box 9, Folder 26)
- IBEW Telephone Industry Survey, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Grievance Procedures (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Kappert Grievance, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Perspectives by Bell of Pennsylvania, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence and Reports (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Local 41 Petition Non-Participation (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Calendar, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Calendar from Representative Doug Walgren, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Communication Workers Training Fund (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Telecommunications International Union Collective Bargaining Handbook, March 1980 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania Folders (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Grievance Time Table, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Miscellaneous Records (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Communication Workers of America National Legislative-Political Conference, April 8-12, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Communication Workers of America Publications, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Publications (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Quality of Work Life Pittsburgh Division Customer Services (Box 10, Folder 3)
- How to Get Every Cent Uncle Sam Owes You! by Mark Weiss, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Communications Workers of America Information Strategy and Plan (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- CWA-COPE (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Communications Workers of America Leading the Way (Box 10, Folder 8)
- TWA Calendar, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Union Voice on Plant Closing Legislation, February 1982 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Barriers to Resolution at District Level of Grievances Filed Under the FTWP Contract: The Views of District Level Managers and Union Local Presidents, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- F.S.W. (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous Pamphlets (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Research Institute Recommendations, Individual Tax Return Guide, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Stress by Blue Cross Association, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Agreement between Local 827 International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers and New Jersey Bell Telephone Company, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Racial (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Forbes Health Maintenance Plan (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Organizing and Anti-Raid by John W. Shaughnessy, Jr., President of Telecommunications International Union (Box 10, Folder 19)
- McGuire Scholarship, 1962, 1964, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Noise Improvement (Box 10, Folder 21)
- National Association of Manufacturers (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Community Services (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Reopeners Wage (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Referendums (Box 10, Folder 25)
- United Way Fund, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Company Reorganization, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Cab Fare, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Vacation Selection, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Veterans (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Vacations, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Vacation, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Telecommunications International Union Job Evaluation, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Records, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Representatives Meeting (Box 11, Folder 8)
- F.W. Roch, Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Directory Assistance, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Rate Increase, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Election of Officers of Labor Organizations by the US Department of Labor (Box 11, Folder 13)
- ESS Committee Meeting Atlantic City, NJ, May 5, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Wage Improvements, August 5, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Minutes of Joint Conference Union Bargaining Committee and Bell Telephone Company, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Agreement between Mid-Penn Telephone Corporation and Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania Local 103, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- COPE Materials, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence and Reports (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Summer Help, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Services (Box 11, Folder 21-22)
- Agreement between Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania and Blue Cross of Greater Philadelphia, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Schedule of Fee Allowances, Pennsylvania Blue Shield (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Test Center Title Survey (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Service Center Titles Study (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Convention, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Resolution Data (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Referendums (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Registration, 1964, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Convention, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Letters Missing from New Contract Books (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Company Letters regarding Collective Bargaining, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Communications Serviceman (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Convention, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Cost of Living (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Veterans Reemployment Rights (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Monthly Grievance Summary (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Western Area Relations Program (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Wage Reopener, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Hospitals (Box 12, Folder 13-15)
- Executive Joint Meeting, November 8, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Blue Shield Experimental Fee Schedule, March 11, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Hospital, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Summer Hiring (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Western Electric Work Jurisdiction (Box 13, Folder 3)
- FTWP News, August 1972 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Francis Weber (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Agnes Russell (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Harold "Russ" Dunn (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Charles Conkel (Box 13, Folder 8)
- John Wiegl (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Convention, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 10)